<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~d/styles/atom10full.xsl"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0">

    <title type="html">Blogs@Intel</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://blogs.intel.com/"/>

    <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011://4</id>
    <subtitle>Innovative online dialogues</subtitle>










    <updated>2011-04-14T09:06:18Z</updated>




    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"
        href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/IntelBlogs"/>
    <feedburner:info uri="intelblogs"/>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="hub"
        href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/"/>
    <feedburner:emailServiceId>IntelBlogs</feedburner:emailServiceId>
    <feedburner:feedburnerHostname>http://feedburner.google.com</feedburner:feedburnerHostname>
    <entry>
        <title type="html">Tablet Innovation: Today and Tomorrow</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/vBeLPfUILHA/tablet_innovation_today_and_to.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/technology//10.4675</id>

        <published>2011-04-14T08:12:16Z</published>

        <updated>2011-04-14T08:22:15Z</updated>

        <summary type="html">This week at the Intel Developer Forum (IDF) in Beijing, Doug Davis, GM
            of the newly formed Netbook and Tablet Group, took to the stage outlining Intel’s plan
            to accelerate the Atom product line roadmap. He boldly claimed that Intel...</summary>

        <author>

            <name>Krystal Temple</name>


        </author>



        <category term="mobile_devices" label="mobile_devices"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/mobile-devices//"/>

        <category term="atom" label="atom" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>


        <category term="idfb11" label="idfb11" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>

        <category term="tablet" label="tablet" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;This week at
            the Intel Developer Forum (IDF) in Beijing, Doug Davis, GM of the newly formed Netbook
            and Tablet Group, took to the stage outlining Intel&amp;#8217;s plan to accelerate the
            Atom product line roadmap. He boldly claimed that Intel will begin to move faster than
            Moore&amp;#8217;s Law to bring new Intel Atom products to market based on three process
            technology generations over the next three years.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This speed of
            development and innovation will help push Intel ahead of the pack in the tablet market.
            Today, the dialogue around tablets is focused on battery life - for good reason. The
            newly launched &lt;a
            href="http://newsroom.intel.com/community/intel_newsroom/blog/2011/04/11/new-intel-atom-processor-for-tablets-spurs-companion-computing-device-innovation?cid=rss-258152-c1-266165"&gt;Atom
            Z670 (codenamed &amp;#8220;Oak Trail&amp;#8221;) &lt;/a&gt; provides up-to all day
            battery life1 - but as Intel begins this acceleration, battery life will quickly become
            a moot point. What was &amp;#8220;all-day&amp;#8221; will become all week or even all
            month battery life. Once this happens, Intel believes the key differentiation in tablets
            and other connected devices will be found in the features that are integrated into the
            silicon, and pure performance which enables a range of consumer benefits. This
            traditionally has been, and continues to be, Intel&amp;#8217;s strength. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;This industry is in the early stages of development, and has yet to realize its
            full potential. We believe that what lies ahead is far greater than what we&amp;#8217;ve
            seen so far. With the launch of the Atom Z670 processor this week, we showcased a
            variety of new tablet innovations, including the &lt;a
            href="http://newsroom.intel.com/community/intel_newsroom/blog/2011/04/11/new-intel-atom-processor-for-tablets-spurs-companion-computing-device-innovation?cid=rss-258152-c1-266165"&gt;Razer
            Switchblade&lt;/a&gt; gaming device, which incorporates a multi-touch screen with a
            dynamic keyboard that adapts and changes with the games being played.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Once was only for consumers, tablets are also finding their way into the
            workplace more and more. Traditional vertical businesses like healthcare are using
            tablets to help increase efficiency, improve productivity and save time. &lt;a
            href="http://www.motioncomputing.com/"&gt;Motion Computing&amp;#8217;s&lt;/a&gt; mobile
            clinical assistant is one such example of how tablets allow medical staff to directly
            input data into patients&amp;#8217; electronic files and avoid paper charting.
            &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the future, tablets may not even look like they do today. Other
            &amp;#8220;hybrid-like&amp;#8221; devices will offer consumers the choice of designs
            that flip, swivel, spin and slide providing both touch-screen and keyboard interfaces.
            &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With so many new, innovative uses, and designs in store for tablets
            and other companion devices, one thing is clear: Intel&amp;#8217;s current and future
            technologies will play a key role in the tablet market segment today and in the
            future.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What do you want from your next tablet? &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;1Software and workloads used in performance tests may have been optimized for
            performance only on Intel microprocessors. Performance tests, such as SYSmark and
            MobileMark, are measured using specific computer systems, components, software,
            operations and functions. Any change to any of those factors may cause the results to
            vary. You should consult other information and performance tests to assist you in fully
            evaluating your contemplated purchases, including the performance of that product when
            combined with other products. For more information go to
            http://www.intel.com/performance.&lt;/p&gt; Comments (0) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/vBeLPfUILHA" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TechnologyIntel/~3/rL_5LKQkgRE/tablet_innovation_today_and_to.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Technology Rocks: Yes, And You Make the Impossible, Possible</title>

        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/gjrHvCWYIxc/"/>
        <id>http://scoop.intel.com/?p=2575</id>

        <published>2011-04-13T05:00:09Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-13T05:00:09Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>


            <name>Marcia Hansen</name>


        </author>



        <category term="inspiration" label="inspiration"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> Here at Intel, there
            are a number of posters that various groups have hung around on cube walls and in
            conference rooms that are designed to build optimism and help us feel empowered and
            energetic about the work that we do here. On the way to my desk, I pass a conference
            room with a [...] &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=52EihOHPC20:f4zR8g_6DqM:yIl2AUoC8zA"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=52EihOHPC20:f4zR8g_6DqM:qj6IDK7rITs"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=52EihOHPC20:f4zR8g_6DqM:F7zBnMyn0Lo"
            /&gt; &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/gjrHvCWYIxc" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/intel/scoop/~3/52EihOHPC20/</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">The Evolution of the Internet In Your TV</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/FSyWkWWytXo/"/>
        <id>http://scoop.intel.com/?p=2543</id>

        <published>2011-04-12T15:24:26Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-12T15:24:26Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Corvida Raven</name>


        </author>




        <category term="Widgets" label="Widgets"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> The concept of
            bringing the internet to the TV has come a long way in terms of functionality and
            design. Remember when everyone went crazy over TV widgets in 2008? TV widgets were
            introduced as early as 2006 through Verizon FIOS. Limited in so many ways with basic
            weather and traffic info, even photos and [...] &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=gUWT69pRWR4:hCMAfrSD31E:yIl2AUoC8zA"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=gUWT69pRWR4:hCMAfrSD31E:qj6IDK7rITs"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=gUWT69pRWR4:hCMAfrSD31E:F7zBnMyn0Lo"
            /&gt; &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/FSyWkWWytXo" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/intel/scoop/~3/gUWT69pRWR4/</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>


    <entry>
        <title type="html">Mobile Monday London – one week to go</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/OLf_bU5S28c/3492"/>
        <id>3492 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-12T05:11:03Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-12T05:11:03Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Softtalkmobile</name>


        </author>



        <category term="EUPost" label="EUPost"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;Mark your
            diaries, demo night is returning to Mobile Monday London.&lt;br /&gt; It’s a bit later
            than planned – the 18th of April, at CBI, Centrepoint, London – but they’ve got some
            juicy demos lined up. It’s going to be popular for sure.&lt;br /&gt; If you haven’t
            signed up to attend then don’t waste time – word has it that this MoMo is going to shake
            a few demo mojos.&lt;br /&gt; You can sign up and RSVP at &lt;a
            href="http://momolo.org"&gt;http://momolo.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/node/3492"&gt;read more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/OLf_bU5S28c" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/node/3492</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">From Intel Developer Forum (IDF) Beijing: New Industry Collaborations in
            China</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/UovZl3j7Ty8/3485"/>
        <id>3485 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-11T19:48:03Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-11T19:48:03Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>gunjan-rawal</name>


        </author>



        <category term="Atom" label="Atom"/>



        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/node/3485"&gt;read more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/UovZl3j7Ty8" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/node/3485</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>

        <title type="html">IESC Vietnam: Making an Impact with Orphans</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/oNBl17B6Xwc/good_morning_from_vietnam.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/csr//16.4668</id>

        <published>2011-04-11T13:08:25Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-11T15:15:46Z</updated>

        <summary type="html">As part of Intel’s ongoing commitment to improving education through
            the effective use of technology, Intel’s Education Market Platforms Group (EMPG)
            launched the Intel Education Service Corps (IESC) in September 2009. This program is a
            short-term service and career development...</summary>

        <author>

            <name>Jeanne Forbis</name>


        </author>



        <category term="education" label="education" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/education//"/>

        <category term="general_csr" label="general_csr"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/general-csr//"/>

        <category term="classmatepc" label="classmatepc" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="csr" label="csr" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>


        <category term="education" label="education" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="iesc" label="iesc" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="intel_education_service_corps" label="intel_education_service_corps"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/assets_c/2011/04/Vietnamone-thumb-300x170.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;As
            part of Intel&amp;#8217;s ongoing commitment to improving education through the
            effective use of technology, Intel&amp;#8217;s Education Market Platforms Group (EMPG)
            launched the &lt;a
            href="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/2009/09/announcing_the_intel_education.php"&gt;Intel
            Education Service Corps (IESC)&lt;/a&gt; in September 2009. This program is a short-term
            service and career development opportunity, for a select group of Intel employees to
            travel to a developing country to directly support the deployment of Intel-powered &lt;a
            href="http://www.classmatepc.com/"&gt;classmate PCs&lt;/a&gt;. Sarah Frawley, an
            Automation Engineer from Ireland, recaps her team&amp;#8217;s first few days in
            Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(In photo left to right: Gabe, Ben, Marissa, Sarah, Tad,
            Bao)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good Morning Vietnam&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;by
            Sarah Frawley&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am one of five Intel employees that has
            just arrived in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam as part of the Intel Education Service Corps
            to work with the non-governmental organization (NGO) Orphans Overseas to help with their
            &lt;a href="http://www.orphanimpact.org/"&gt;Orphan Impact project&lt;/a&gt;. Orphan
            Impact has been delivering computer training to 800 children in 12 orphanages across 9
            provinces in Vietnam since 2009 using &lt;a
            href="http://www.classmatepc.com/"&gt;Intel-powered classmate PCs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;My name is Sarah Frawley (Automation Engineer) and I will be working on this
            team with 4 other Intel Employees: Marissa Mertzic (Process Engineer), Bao Nguyen
            (Microprocessor Product Developer), Ben Young (Business Development Manager on 4G/
            Wimax) and Gabe Schnaubelt (Technology &amp;amp; Manufacturing Group Software Engineer).
            Gabe, Ben and Bao are all based in Oregon, Marissa is from Massachusetts, and I am based
            in Ireland. Bao is originally from South Vietnam and has been helping us all with the
            language translations and with ordering local food and especially requesting gluten-free
            for Marissa!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We have been working together for ~30 hours the last 5
            weeks preparing for the assignment incuding virtual training, face to face training and
            regular meetings to sort out our logistics and project goals. The training phase of the
            project was conducted in parallel with our existing roles at Intel.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/vietnamtwo.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;We all arrived in Ho Chi Minh City April 1st when some of us met for the first
            time while others had met at the face to face training day in Santa Clara a couple of
            weeks back. Temperature has been ranging from 25 -37 degrees Celsius with humidity
            averaging 83% so it&amp;#8217;s pretty hot and sticky!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We are all
            very eager and excited in getting started with the project. We met Tad, our NGO
            representative for the Orphan Impact project and went through the agenda for the next 2
            weeks. Our team began to decide how best to tackle the tasks that were ahead of us. We
            will be working with LEGO kits which will be used in the classes for the first time. We
            are also planning lessons, revising existing lessons, and focusing especially on
            training the local teachers on 21st century education skills. Gabe and I both have
            technical backgrounds and began going through some initial setup and configuration on
            the classmate PCs, as well as installing classroom management software which will
            provide new capabilities to the students and teachers within the Vietnam orphanages. We
            also worked with an experienced classmate PC representative at Intel Singapore, Bernd
            Nordhausen, who gave us some useful advice with getting the classmate PCs
            configured.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On Day 2 we met some of the local Ho Chi Minh City Orphan
            Impact teachers, and Ben, Bao and Marissa got involved in their lesson-planning for the
            week ahead. The teachers travel by motorcycle to each of the centres every week to roll
            out 3 hours of computer training. They bring all the classmate PCs and equipment with
            them which results in 30 machines getting spread across all the Ho Chi Minh City centres
            and orphanages which reach up to 109 students. That evening we visited our first
            orphanage in Binh An which is 15 kilometers from downtown Ho Chi Minh City. We got to
            observe the local Orphan Impact teachers teaching a class on Microsoft Office. The kids
            have been using the classmate PCs for over 6 months and are pretty comfortable with
            their navigation and enthusiastic about learning more. Our team had some fruit to give
            each of the kids and there were smiles all round at the end of class.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;The next day we had 2 orphanage visits. Marissa and I got the chance to ride to
            one of the centres on the back of a motor bike wearing a &amp;#8220;Winne the
            Pooh&amp;#8221; helmet with one of the Vietnamese teachers which was pretty exciting,
            especially at rush hour! There are over 3 million motor bikes in Ho Chi Minh City making
            it the main mode of transport. While she was riding on the back of motor bike, Marissa
            asked her driver Bang, a local Vietnamese teacher, if she had been in many accidents and
            Bang replied &amp;#8220;Many!&amp;#8221; Marissa made it through the ride ok
            regardless.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We went to Tu Xuong in the morning which is a centre for
            teenagers ranging between 14-18 years of age. Some kids attend the classes by day and
            travel home to their families at night and are usually from economically disadvantaged
            backgrounds (for example, single-parent families where the parent is sick or disabled
            and unable to work). Some of them walk for 2 hours to get to the centre and others cycle
            for 1.5 hours. The kids at this centre have been taught English for the last few years
            and they all introduced themselves in English and told us what they would like to be
            when they grow up. We had some budding song artists among us. Our team introduced
            ourselves also in English, apart from Bao who was able to introduce himself in
            Vietnamese.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/vietnamthree.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our
            afternoon was spent observing a lesson at an orphanage in Thu Duc. The kids here are
            either attending the orphanage full-time or are one of many undocumented kids who are
            unable to attend public schools and attend this one by day. This was a busy and noisy
            centre with other classes and break times taking place nearby the area where our
            classmate PC lesson was happening. However this did not faze the students at all and
            they were all focused on the Microsoft Word activity for their lesson. We chatted with
            some of the kids at the oprhanage, again a lot of them had enough English to introduce
            themselves and were also keen to find out things about us and they all loved my
            sunglasses.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The last couple of days have given us an insight into the
            exposure to technology that these kids have been given by the Orphan Impact project and
            the opportunity it will give them to further their education. One of the Orphan Impact
            teachers, Thao, is a previous student from one of the centres here. She is an
            inspiration to the existing students on the many career paths available once they leave
            the centres. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;P.S. Click &lt;a
            href="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/iesc"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to catch up on the
            adventures, experiences and learnings from the 14 previous Intel Education Service Corps
            teams and the other two teams who are working right now in Kenya and India. &lt;/p&gt;
            Comments (0) &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/oNBl17B6Xwc"
            height="1" width="1"/&gt;</content>

        <feedburner:origLink>http://blogs.intel.com/csr/2011/04/good_morning_from_vietnam.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Calling all web app developers…we’ve got something for you!</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/NRJc84fTISU/calling-all-web-app-developers-we-ve-got-something-you"/>
        <id>3405 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-11T13:03:59Z</published>

        <updated>2011-04-11T13:03:59Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Rhonda Peters</name>


        </author>



        <category term="web apps" label="web apps"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://twitter.com/share"&gt;Tweet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The
            Intel AppUp℠ developer program is excited to announce a new opportunity for web app
            developers to transform web apps into Intel AppUp℠ center apps. This opportunity, called
            Intel AppUp™ encapsulator, allows web app developers to expand their customer base and
            revenue potential by making an app from their existing web code that is compatible and
            available for the Intel AppUp℠ center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/03/31/calling-all-web-app-developers-we-ve-got-something-you"&gt;read
            more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/NRJc84fTISU" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/03/31/calling-all-web-app-developers-we-ve-got-something-you</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">My Application Lab Experience</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/LOQPwSql0Qw/3479"/>
        <id>3479 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-11T11:34:31Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-11T11:34:31Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Brian_Intel</name>


        </author>



        <category term="MeeGo" label="MeeGo"/>



        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;Well
            I&amp;apos;m spreading my wings on two fronts - my first blog and the first time
            I&amp;apos;ll be running the show for an Intel AppUp Application Lab. My new role is to
            manage the application labs that we put on for our user communities in the Intel AppUp
            developer program. Fortunately I&amp;apos;m lucky to be surrounded by some pretty
            awesome people here to help me on my journey! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Trial by fire. On the
            job training. Thrown to the wolves. These were some of the thoughts that have entered my
            mind in the 3 months that I&amp;apos;ve been here.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/node/3479"&gt;read more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/LOQPwSql0Qw" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/node/3479</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">AppUp Developers WANTED for APPNATION 2011! </title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/D_FS6Ax36S8/appup-developers-wanted-appnation-2011"/>
        <id>3471 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-08T08:45:22Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-08T08:45:22Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Gina M Bovara</name>


        </author>



        <category term="training" label="training"/>



        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;br /&gt;
            How&amp;apos;d you like to have your own dedicated stage to showcase your apps or ideas
            for fellow developers and industry experts at APPNATION 2011 in San Francisco? read more
            &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/D_FS6Ax36S8" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/08/appup-developers-wanted-appnation-2011</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">The Geek Travel Guide: Stop 1 – California Bay area science and
            technology museums</title>

        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/WBK0V2wfIeE/"/>
        <id>http://scoop.intel.com/?p=2560</id>

        <published>2011-04-07T05:00:27Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-07T05:00:27Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>


            <name>Marcia Hansen</name>


        </author>



        <category term="road trip" label="road trip"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> I’ve been daydreaming
            about ways I could convince my employer to fund a summer road trip spent touring cool
            science and technology centers, and sharing all my travels with you via this blog. Until
            I can sell that plan, I’ll have to content myself writing blog posts about my road trip
            travel dreams. I hope [...] &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=vnaWVBmQ6pg:dUcECkMuZl0:yIl2AUoC8zA"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=vnaWVBmQ6pg:dUcECkMuZl0:qj6IDK7rITs"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=vnaWVBmQ6pg:dUcECkMuZl0:F7zBnMyn0Lo"
            /&gt; &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/WBK0V2wfIeE" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/intel/scoop/~3/vnaWVBmQ6pg/</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Are Our Mobile Devices Making Us Rude?</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/LI5dxXR4AiA/"/>
        <id>http://scoop.intel.com/?p=2548</id>

        <published>2011-04-06T14:10:37Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-06T14:10:37Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Jessica Hansen</name>


        </author>




        <category term="mobile computing" label="mobile computing"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> How many mobile
            technology devices (laptops, netbooks, smartphones, tablets) do you own? How would you
            rate your mobile manners when using the devices around others? According to a recent
            Mobile Etiquette survey sponsored by Intel and conducted by Ipsos, 75 percent of U.S.
            adults believe mobile manners are becoming worse (compared to 2009, when Intel [...]
            &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=NeH5Nvckp4I:xzMqdoiT34s:yIl2AUoC8zA"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=NeH5Nvckp4I:xzMqdoiT34s:qj6IDK7rITs"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=NeH5Nvckp4I:xzMqdoiT34s:F7zBnMyn0Lo"
            /&gt; &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/LI5dxXR4AiA" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/intel/scoop/~3/NeH5Nvckp4I/</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>


    <entry>
        <title type="html">Choosing the right finance model for your app</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/UkWLrHXpcOI/choosing-right-finance-model-your-app"/>
        <id>3452 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-06T05:57:06Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-06T05:57:06Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Softtalkmobile</name>


        </author>



        <category term="payments" label="payments"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;You might be
            tempted to think you can create your app now and worry about how you make money with it
            later. The problem with that is that the way that people use your app will have an
            influence on how you can make money with it. There are several options available to you:
            &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sell the app: This model is the most obvious, and means you need to
            convince people the app is worth buying and demonstrate that it is after they have
            downloaded the app.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/06/choosing-right-finance-model-your-app"&gt;read
            more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/UkWLrHXpcOI" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>

        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/06/choosing-right-finance-model-your-app</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Interview with Dmitry Rizshkov / Intelloware</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/5mOvat15AZ8/interview-dmitry-rizshkov-intelloware"/>
        <id>3445 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-05T00:57:32Z</published>

        <updated>2011-04-05T00:57:32Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>zehjotkah</name>


        </author>



        <category term="MeeGo" label="MeeGo"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;We are here
            together with Dmitry Rizskov, better known as &lt;a
            href="http://www.appup.com/applications/publisher-Intelloware"&gt;Intelloware&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br
            /&gt; Dmitry released some really cool Apps for Windows and MeeGo in the recent
            past.&lt;br /&gt;During the next minutes we&amp;apos;ll try to find out why Dmitry is
            developing for MeeGo and what he thinks about the Intel AppUp Developer Program.&lt;br
            /&gt; Have fun!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/04/interview-dmitry-rizshkov-intelloware"&gt;read
            more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/5mOvat15AZ8" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/04/interview-dmitry-rizshkov-intelloware</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Summing up Texas Linux Fest 2011</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/lcu2fPEXkDg/summing-texas-linux-fest-2011"/>
        <id>3434 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-04T16:04:31Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-04T16:04:31Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Randall Arnold</name>


        </author>



        <category term="Texas" label="Texas"/>



        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;This past
            Saturday I had the honor of speaking at the 2011 &lt;a
            href="http://texaslinuxfest.org/"&gt;Texas Linux Fest&lt;/a&gt; in Austin, Texas. You
            can read &lt;a
            href="http://tabulacrypticum.wordpress.com/2011/04/04/texas-linux-fest-2011/"&gt;the
            details in my main blog&lt;/a&gt;, but the essential point is that it was a productive
            event for me and I&amp;apos;m glad I got the opportunity to go. I&amp;apos;ll post my
            presentation soon.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For a one-day conference, quite a bit was covered.
            One thing missing, though was &lt;a
            href="http://meego.com"&gt;MeeGo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/04/summing-texas-linux-fest-2011"&gt;read
            more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/lcu2fPEXkDg" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>

        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/04/summing-texas-linux-fest-2011</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Intel MeeGo 1.2 Tablet UX now open sourced. This and more now on
            MeeGo.com </title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/NhVCYrLofHc/intel-meego-12-tablet-ux-now-open-sourced-available-meegocom"/>
        <id>3426 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-04-04T11:17:16Z</published>

        <updated>2011-04-04T11:17:16Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>Bob Duffy</name>


        </author>



        <category term="tablet" label="tablet"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p /&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Mid February of this year, Intel released the MeeGo 1.2 Tablet UX pre-alpha to
            our developer community. And now a month later we are happy to announce that this
            release has been fully open sourced, where it is supported and available under the open
            source MeeGo project at MeeGo.com.read more&lt;/p&gt; &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/NhVCYrLofHc" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/04/04/intel-meego-12-tablet-ux-now-open-sourced-available-meegocom</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Weekend Gaming – Medieval Times</title>

        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/OMkyrIWB1Hk/"/>
        <id>http://scoop.intel.com/?p=1956</id>

        <published>2011-04-01T14:03:35Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-01T14:03:35Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>


            <name>Regina Wu</name>


        </author>



        <category term="pc games" label="pc games"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> The weekend is here
            again! I just got a copy of The Sims Medieval, the newest addition to the Sims
            franchise. I’ve been a big fan of the Sims for a long time, and it will be great to play
            in a different setting. While trying to install the game, I actually got an error [...]
            &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=Xg1xHIZueds:uybtR-RSKDM:yIl2AUoC8zA"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=Xg1xHIZueds:uybtR-RSKDM:qj6IDK7rITs"
            /&gt; &lt;a
            href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/intel/scoop?a=Xg1xHIZueds:uybtR-RSKDM:F7zBnMyn0Lo"
            /&gt; &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/OMkyrIWB1Hk" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/intel/scoop/~3/Xg1xHIZueds/</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Connection 11</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/aa0CRzQmckk/connection_11.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/csr//16.4637</id>

        <published>2011-04-01T10:58:00Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-01T11:33:43Z</updated>

        <summary type="html">iPhones, iPads, Blackberries, netbooks. Being connected has become a
            central theme in our lives. With an arsenal of gadgets, we access the Internet and each
            other 24/7. For my role working in CSR, staying connected is more than just
            being...</summary>

        <author>

            <name>Revital Bitan</name>


            <uri>http://blogs.intel.com/csr/2007/06/profile_revital_bitan.php</uri>


        </author>



        <category term="general_csr" label="general_csr"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/general-csr//"/>

        <category term="csr" label="csr" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="digitaldivide" label="digitaldivide"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="intel" label="intel" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="youbridge" label="youbridge" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;iPhones,
            iPads, Blackberries, netbooks. Being connected has become a central theme in our lives.
            With an arsenal of gadgets, we access the Internet and each other 24/7. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;For my role working in CSR, staying connected is more than just being able to
            read emails while riding the commuter train. It is also about connecting people in order
            to bridge gaps. Rich/poor, educated/illiterate, healthy/sick. It is our mission at Intel
            to transcend these divides to make the world a better, fairer place. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;In my role working in CSR, one of the things that I look for are examples of
            Intel employees finding innovative ways to connect with external partners to help
            address social challenges. My colleague, Kurt De Buck from our Intel Belgium
            office,worked with his group to kick start the Wonderful Digital Future initiative by
            donating laptops to 11 university students (why 11? Because this year is 2011!) at the
            International Health Science University (IHSU) in Uganda. Wonderful Digital Future
            focuses on programs in which Europe and Africa reach out to each other. &lt;a
            href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UwmOhMyUtm8&amp;amp;feature=related"&gt;Watch the
            video&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bridging the digital
            divide&lt;/strong&gt; Kurt&amp;#8217;s group donated part of the money designated for
            New Year&amp;#8217;s customer gifts to YouBridge.org. YouBridge, a Belgian initiative,
            allows people to give new laptops to students in developing countries. The donor chooses
            who will receive the laptop and then joins an online social network of donors and
            recipients. The beauty of YouBridge is it lets people connect across physical and
            economic barriers. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For both donor and recipient, &lt;a
            href="http://www.youbridge.org/"&gt;YouBridge&lt;/a&gt; opens a new
            &amp;#8216;digital&amp;#8217; window to the world. As Pieter Dewinter from YouBridge
            describes it: &amp;#8220;At YouBridge, we are very positive about this project with
            Intel. Not only because Intel is one of the few companies where CSR is a genuine and
            fundamental part of the corporate philosophy, but also because of the direct impact our
            collaboration has: the TV-spot was made possible and for 11 young and ambitious people,
            thanks to Intel we have made a true difference in their lives and given them a window to
            the world. We hope this is just the start of a great partnership!&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Also Intel&amp;#8217;s customers, whose &amp;#8220;gifts&amp;#8221; have been
            donated in part to this charity, also get something from the initiative: a mouse pad
            featuring pictures of the 11 participating students, allowing them to see the
            transformative power of technology and learn about these impressive students. &lt;/p&gt;
            Comments (0) &lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/aa0CRzQmckk"
            height="1" width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://blogs.intel.com/csr/2011/04/connection_11.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Intel &amp; Smart TV: An Interview from IPTV World Forum</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/hxyQTP5OSp4/intel_smart_tv_an_interview_fr.php"/>

        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/technology//10.4636</id>

        <published>2011-04-01T03:22:11Z</published>
        <updated>2011-04-01T03:29:27Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"
            ><![CDATA[Intel had a great show at IP&amp;TV World Forum 2011 last week, lots of positive responses to our work from the industry players. I managed to catch up with the General Manager of IPTV at Intel, Mr Keith Wehmeyer, who...]]></summary>

        <author>

            <name>Paul Tapp</name>



            <uri>http://www.facebook.com/IntelSmartTV</uri>

        </author>



        <category term="digital_home" label="digital_home"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/digital-home//"/>

        <category term="technologies_for_our_lives" label="technologies_for_our_lives"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/add-category//"/>

        <category
            term="intelsmarttvsmarttviptviptvworldforumlondonvodottboxeefreeorangetelecomitaliacubovisionbouygues"
            label="intelsmarttvsmarttviptviptvworldforumlondonvodottboxeefreeorangetelecomitaliacubovisionbouygues"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;Intel had a
            great show at IP&amp;amp;TV World Forum 2011 last week, lots of positive responses to
            our work from the industry players. I managed to catch up with the General Manager of
            IPTV at Intel, Mr Keith Wehmeyer, who shares his thoughts with us on the direction of
            Smart TV in this short video.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Comments (0) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/hxyQTP5OSp4" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TechnologyIntel/~3/cK5X3Ukv_2k/intel_smart_tv_an_interview_fr.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Early Thoughts on Proposed ACO Rules</title>

        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/JQKeQnuo5DE/early_thoughts_on_proposed_aco_rules.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/healthcare//38.4635</id>

        <published>2011-03-31T21:16:04Z</published>
        <updated>2011-03-31T21:16:47Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"
            ><![CDATA[ Hear ye, hear ye, read all about it! For those of you who have been waiting with bated breath (you know who you are!), the U.S. Department of Health &amp; Human Services has just published the proposed rules and...]]></summary>

        <author>


            <name>Eric Dishman</name>


        </author>



        <category term="healthcare" label="healthcare" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare//"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/">
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hear ye, hear ye, read all about it! For
            those of you who have been waiting with bated breath (you know who you are!), the U.S.
            Department of Health &amp;amp; Human Services has just published the proposed rules and
            guidelines for Accountable Care Organizations (ACOs) and the Medicare Shared Savings
            Program (SSP). You can download the 428-page document &lt;a
            href="http://www.ofr.gov/OFRUpload/OFRData/2011-07880_PI.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and see
            the official press release &lt;a
            href="http://www.hhs.gov/news/press/2011pres/03/20110331a.html"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
            Though, unless you are a policy or healthcare reform geek (which I guess I am becoming,
            frighteningly enough), you might want to wait for the inevitable summaries to be done by
            various consulting firms, non-profits, and individuals. I will post some of the good
            ones here when I see them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These
            rule-makings around ACOs are a major component of the Affordable Care Act signed by
            President Obama last March, though most citizens and press outside of the healthcare
            industry have no clue what this is all about. ACOs are the primary mechanism for
            beginning to shift the American healthcare system from a volume-driven to a value-driven
            paradigm. In other words, today, the majority of healthcare is paid based on the volume
            of face-to-face visits, labwork, and prescriptions generated more than the value of the
            care provided. And these payments occur regardless of whether the treatments given (and
            charged for) are effective or helpful. The strategic intent of the health reform bill is
            to shift to a mode of payment that focuses much more on rewarding the
            &lt;i&gt;quality&lt;/i&gt; of care over the volume of care. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;There are three primary aims of these reform
            efforts (sometimes referred to as "the triple aims" or as "Berwick's triple aims" named
            for Don Berwick, the current Administrator for the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid
            Services). First, the goal is to provide better care for individuals. Second is to
            improve care for populations. And third is to lower the growth in healthcare costs and
            expenditures. ACOs are one of many tools to achieve these three aims, and healthcare
            providers and companies have been eager to see what the Secretary would propose as the
            specific requirements for becoming an ACO.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Basically, an ACO is a group of care providers--usually centered around primary
            care physicians--who commit, according to the proposed rules released today, for a
            minimum of three years to manage the overall care and costs of at least 5000 Medicare
            patients. And the ACO has to have a legal structure (though they are very flexible on
            the different kinds of structures permissible) that allows the organization to receive
            and distribute payments to all its care providers in the management of the care.
            &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So imagine, for example, several
            physician practices, a hospital, and a home care agency within a particular town coming
            together to form an ACO to care for at least 5000 Medicare beneficiaries in that
            community. They would be paid what is often referred to as a "bundled" or "global
            payment" annually to care for all of the health needs of those patients, and they could
            participate in the Shared Savings Program by which they could get bonuses based on
            helping to reduce healthcare expenditures while boosting quality. Lest you think these
            providers would just ignore the needs of the sickest patients to keep their costs low
            and leave more shared savings in their pockets (and I should say that I have never met
            any clinicians in our 10+ years of fieldwork who would be so inclined--the majority are
            good people who went into medicine to &lt;i&gt;help&lt;/i&gt; people), there are clear
            rules and data-driven quality measurement mechanisms that prevent that from
            happening.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am particularly heartened
            to see some of the following language in the proposed rules:&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;• The ACO shall define processes to promote
            evidence-based medicine and&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;patient engagement, report on quality and
            cost measures, and coordinate care, such as through the use of telehealth, remote
            patient monitoring, and other such enabling technologies (p.17) &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;• The ACO shall demonstrate to the Secretary that
            it meets patient-centeredness&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;criteria specified by the Secretary,
            such as the use of patient and caregiver assessments or the use of individualized care
            plans (p.17)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;• An ACO will manage
            resources carefully and respectfully. It will ensure continual waste reduction, and that
            every step in care adds value to the beneficiary. An ACO will be able to make
            investments where investments count, and move resources to meet beneficiaries' needs.
            Because of its capabilities with respect to prevention and anticipation, especially for
            chronically ill people, an ACO will be able to continually reduce its dependence on
            inpatient care. Instead, its patients will more likely be able to be home, where they
            often want to be, and, during a hospital admission, they receive assurance that their
            discharges will be well coordinated, and that they will not return due to avoidable
            complications (p. 25)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;• An ACO will be
            proactive by reaching out to patients with reminders and&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;advice that
            can help them stay healthy and let them know when it is time for a checkup or a test
            (p.25)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;• An ACO will collect, evaluate,
            and use data on health care processes and&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;outcomes sufficiently to
            measure what it achieves for beneficiaries and communities over time and use such data
            to improve care delivery and patient outcomes (p. 25)&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;• An ACO will be innovative in the service of the
            three-part aim of better care for&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;individuals, better health for
            populations, and lower growth in expenditures. It will draw upon the best, most advanced
            models of care, using modern technologies, including telehealth and electronic health
            records, and other tools to continually reinvent care in the modern age. It will monitor
            and compare its performance to other ACOs, identify and examine new processes for care
            improvement, and adopt those approaches that are demonstrated to be effective
            (p.25)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;While I have several hundred
            more pages to go, my initial read shows some very promising directions. The rules feel
            very innovation-friendly and leave lots of flexibility and experimentation for
            communities to try different approaches to setting up ACOs. The focus on "patient
            engagement" shows a much-needed momentum around providing tools and expectations for
            patients to be a more proactive and responsible party in our own care. The explicit
            references to the use of telehealth and remote patient monitoring and the calling out of
            the need to move care to the home shows that CMS "gets it" in terms of the need to
            "place-shift" (a topic I bring up frequently in this blog) where care occurs away from
            more expensive settings like hospitals. And the requirements for incorporating and using
            data-driven, evidence-based tools to drive best practice care and continuous
            innovation/improvement will help us finally achieve a 21st century healthcare
            infrastructure that is scalable and competitive, internationally.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I will post more of my own and other peoples'
            summaries over the next week. Meanwhile, what say ye?&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; Comments (0) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/JQKeQnuo5DE" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>

        <feedburner:origLink>http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/2011/03/early_thoughts_on_proposed_aco_rules.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">How to integrate AppUp SDK and create RPM package for MeeGo
            applications</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/uja2Qw4hr7g/how-integrate-appup-sdk-and-create-rpm-package-meego-applications"/>
        <id>3401 at http://appdeveloper.intel.com</id>

        <published>2011-03-30T18:28:36Z</published>

        <updated>2011-03-30T18:28:36Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"/>

        <author>

            <name>dmitry-rizshkov</name>


        </author>



        <category term="rpm" label="rpm"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;In this
            article i will show you how to prepare your MeeGo app to be validated in the Intel AppUp
            Center. This article is based on the project from my another article &lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2010/12/24/modern-mobile-applications-qt-and-qml"&gt;Modern
            mobile applications with Qt and QML&lt;/a&gt;. No changes will be made in the project
            source code. Thanks to Qt, our Windows application could be launched on MeeGo without
            any changes in code, all you need is just to recompile it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br
            /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/03/30/how-integrate-appup-sdk-and-create-rpm-package-meego-applications"&gt;read
            more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/uja2Qw4hr7g" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>

        <feedburner:origLink>http://appdeveloper.intel.com/en-us/blog/2011/03/30/how-integrate-appup-sdk-and-create-rpm-package-meego-applications</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Oregon's Opportunity for Innovating Aging: A City Club Follow Up</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/b2gRGCsDtuY/oregons_opportunity_for_innovating_aging_a_city_club_follow_up.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/healthcare//38.4633</id>

        <published>2011-03-30T16:33:38Z</published>

        <updated>2011-03-31T21:42:31Z</updated>

        <summary type="html">Last week I had the honor of speaking to the City Club of Portland, an
            organization founded in 1916 to highlight the diverse opinions, issues, and talents of
            local leaders and organizations. I often hear their Friday Forums on Oregon...</summary>

        <author>

            <name>Eric Dishman</name>


        </author>



        <category term="healthcare" label="healthcare" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare//"/>

        <category term="careinnovations" label="careinnovations"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>


        <category term="cityclubofportland" label="cityclubofportland"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="dishman" label="dishman" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="graytechnologies" label="graytechnologies"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="independentliving" label="independentliving"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="intelpolicy" label="intelpolicy"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="orcatech" label="orcatech" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="tril" label="tril" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;Last week I
            had the honor of speaking to the City Club of Portland, an organization founded in 1916
            to highlight the diverse opinions, issues, and talents of local leaders and
            organizations. I often hear their Friday Forums on Oregon Public Broadcasting radio
            while I am driving home from work, so it was a real treat to be there in person in the
            grand Governor Hotel in downtown Portland. I very much appreciate the City Club members
            inviting me and giving visibility to the important issues of Global Aging and what I
            have frequently referred to in this blog as "gray technologies."&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The title of my talk was "Technological
            Innovation and the Future of Aging"--you can click &lt;a
            href="http://www.pdxcityclub.org/content/future-aging-through-technological-innovation"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;
            to find a free download of the audio cast of the speech--in which I focused on Oregon's
            opportunity to lead in the development of new technologies, services, and jobs that
            promote independent living for our graying population. I shared some of the research
            prototypes and findings that Intel, Oregon Health &amp;amp; Science University (OHSU),
            and the Oregon Center for Aging and Technology (ORCATECH) have developed from our more
            than ten years of exploration into home-based technologies that can help people to
            age-in-place with good health, social engagement, purposefulness, dignity, and
            choice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I promised attendees (and the
            many radio and TV listeners who have been writing to me ever since!) that I would post
            some links where you can find more information. To that end, here are a few that I
            referred to in my talk...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;ORACTECH&lt;/b&gt;, the Oregon Center for Aging and Technology at
            &lt;a href="http://www.orcatech.org/"&gt;www.orcatech.org&lt;/a&gt;, is a
            passion-driven, grass-roots center founded in Oregon Health &amp;amp; Science University
            to help coordinate statewide collaborations around independent living technologies
            amongst universities, companies large and small, non-profits, and government agencies.
            The funding to get this started came from Intel's $3 million dollar donation to OHSU and
            a prestigious NIH Roybal Center Grant awarded to ORCATECH director, Dr. Jeff Kaye and
            his collaborators. You can join the mailing list by emailing &lt;a
            href="mailto:orcatech@ohsu.edu"&gt;orcatech@ohsu.edu&lt;/a&gt; or, if you are local to
            Portland, come join "upcoming events" announced on the web page.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CAST&lt;/b&gt;, the Center for Aging
            Services Technologies at &lt;a
            href="http://www.agingtech.org/"&gt;www.agingtech.org&lt;/a&gt;, is a non-profit
            advocacy organization I helped to develop with the American Association of Homes
            &amp;amp; Services for the Aging who recently changed their name to &lt;a
            href="http://www.leadingage.org/"&gt;LeadingAge&lt;/a&gt;. CAST is a national (or
            actually, now international) version of ORCATECH, designed to bring together providers,
            university researchers, technology companies, and others to help ignite a wide array of
            innovative technologies and services to help seniors to age-in-place from the "home" of
            their choice. Be sure to view the &lt;a
            href="http://www.leadingage.org/article_cast.aspx?id=10153"&gt;free CAST vision
            video&lt;/a&gt; shown to Congress and the last White House Conference on Aging.
            &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The TRIL Center&lt;/b&gt;, or
            Technology Research for Independent Living, at &lt;a
            href="http://www.trilcentre.org/"&gt;www.trilcentre.org&lt;/a&gt; based near Dublin,
            Ireland, is Intel's largest investment in independent living technology research with a
            $30M joint investment with the Irish government. TRIL includes our multidisciplinary
            Intel team and three universities in collaboration with St. James Hospital in Dublin to
            invent and test out these home health and independent living technologies. You can learn
            more about the falls work there at the TRIL Center site, as well as go &lt;a
            href="http://www.shimmer-research.com/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to read more about the Shimmer
            "matchbox-sized wireless computer" I described in the talk. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;ETAC&lt;/b&gt;, the Everyday
            Technologies for Alzheimer's Care initiative, a collaborative program between Intel and
            the national office of the Alzheimer's Association, has published information &lt;a
            href="http://www.alz.org/professionals_and_researchers_everyday_technologies_for_alzheimer_care.asp"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;
            about the grants that we have funded since 2004. This was one of our first programs to
            start funding university research on independent living technologies and has produced a
            great international community of dedicated researchers and entrepreneurs focused on
            Alzheimer's care specifically.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Care Innovations&lt;/b&gt;, at &lt;a
            href="http://www.careinnovations.com/"&gt;www.careinnovations.com&lt;/a&gt;, is the name
            of the newly formed &lt;a
            href="http://newsroom.intel.com/community/intel_newsroom/blog/2011/01/03/ge-and-intels-telehealth-and-independent-living-company-is-operational-today"&gt;joint
            venture&lt;/a&gt; between Intel and GE to produce disease management, independent
            living, and assistive technologies for the home. Full disclosure: I run healthcare
            policy for Care Innovations (in addition to my Intel role). I didn't feature our
            products at the City Club talk because my focus was on the R&amp;amp;D infrastructure
            that Oregon has built, not a commercial for our products. But I don't want to leave the
            impression that everything is stuck in research...Care Innovations (and many other
            companies) is diligently working to get these kinds of aging-in-place solutions to
            market worldwide!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And realizing now
            that I had to fly through my recommendations to the state of Oregon at the end of that
            lecture (I warned everyone that, without PowerPoint, there was no predicting what I
            might say!), I want to highlight some of the main points I tried to make last week. My
            overall thesis was that Oregon has some enormous advantages in trying to become an
            international leader of independent living technologies and jobs. Just as we have with
            Wave Energy and Biotech, our state needs to bluntly ask ourselves as Oregonians what
            future industries we could really lead in?&amp;nbsp; I argue that Oregon is already a
            big fish in the small pond of independent living R&amp;amp;D and that we should put
            forth a state plan to go after this opportunity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;So, why Oregon?&amp;nbsp; What are our particular strengths?&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1) We have a head start: We can build upon the
            foundational technologies, data, and know-how of ORCATECH, OHSU, Intel and many others
            in our state who are recognized leaders internationally in this emerging field. Today,
            we already host numerous Minister of Health and other visitors in our labs, as other
            countries and states come to see what Oregon is doing. Now we need to make sure our own
            state knows the assets we have!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2) We
            have our own fiscal challenges: Oregon itself is already in the top ten of states with
            the highest percentage of an aging population, and we likely face cuts to our Home and
            Community Based services as we, like so many other states, try to balance a budget in
            the midst of a recession. We need independent living and home health technologies just
            to drive up quality and drive down costs of the care for seniors--and people of all
            ages--in our own backyard.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3) We have
            flexibility. Though many of my friends and colleagues in the long term care industry in
            our state would like to see even more flexibility, we need to realize that we have more
            regulatory/licensure freedom to pilot and develop new care models for seniors than do
            many other states. Less red tape for us means faster innovation cycles and learnings
            than many other states can produce!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4)
            We know high tech. There is a large information technology presence here in Oregon to
            draw upon--not just Intel but many other technology companies who have intellectual
            property, innovation methodologies, and entrepreneurs to bring to the challenge of
            addressing Global Aging. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5) We are the
            right size. I believe we are the right size and geography of a state to develop
            independent living technologies and the care models to use them. It is hard to imagine a
            state as large as California or as small as Delaware doing this. With our four million
            citizens living in a mix of rural and urban environments across the state, it is
            conceivable and achievable to build a state-wide strategy and infrastructure to enable
            aging-in-place.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6) We can collaborate
            with Asia. Oregon is already seen as a "gateway to the Pacific Rim" with a wide range of
            trade and research collaborations going on with Asian countries. Having just keynoted to
            the APEC (Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation) meeting just weeks ago in D.C., I can tell
            you that the need and market for independent living solutions in Asia is significant
            given the longevity in many of the countries there. If done right, our state plan for
            Global Aging should foster collaboration and export of our Oregon technologies and
            services to some of these countries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;7)
            We have national political leaders for aging issues. It is rare as I make visits to
            Congress that members know much about gerontology, but when I visit the Oregon
            delegation, they often end up teaching me more than I do them! Senator Wyden has a
            background in gerontology, as does Congressman Peter DeFazio, and both have shown a
            commitment to aging and health reform issues in their political careers. I believe we
            should be leveraging their understanding and leadership on aging issues to make Oregon
            the center of the independent living technology universe!&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;8) We are committed to healthcare reform. I had
            the pleasure of hearing last week's "Think Out Loud" radio segment on OPB that was
            exploring healthcare reform in the state of Oregon. Dr. Bruce Goldberg, head of the
            Oregon Health Authority, was clear (and I couldn't agree more!) that we need to
            transform our culture and infrastructure to do health reform right. At the end of the
            day, aging-in-place is not about technology but about transforming our culture of care
            for seniors, and the technology is simply a tool to help do that. But if we are a state
            prepared to be at the forefront of acute care/hospital/insurance reform, let's make sure
            we do the same for long term care!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;9)
            We have a legacy to uphold. Last but not least, innovating aging is in our blood...is in
            our history...as a state. Oregon is widely credited as the state who invented
            end-of-life or hospice care, which became a national standard and movement. Similarly,
            we are known for pioneering the concept of "assisted living" which is, of course, now
            common-place and taken-for-granted. In many ways, the rest of the country is just
            waiting for Oregon to invent "what's next?" for the care of seniors, so let's not
            disappoint them!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We should make no
            mistake as a state to think that we can rest on our laurels or that we will just end up
            becoming the leader of independent living technologies without investment or a plan.
            Other states are competing to create these technologies and jobs; I have worked with
            officials in New York, Minnesota, California, and Florida who are trying to get their
            act together on this front. I am biased as an Oregonian to want to make sure it happens
            here, but at the end of the day, may the most organized and proactive state win!
            &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So what would my calls to action be
            for Oregon? What should we be doing to capitalize upon this opportunity?&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1. I call upon Governor Kitzhaber to put together
            a commission to develop a state Global Aging response plan. Let's bring together
            industry, community, and academic experts to identify how we can use independent living
            technologies to care for our own elders and families and also evaluate new business and
            job opportunities in this segment. I will certainly volunteer my time to
            participate!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2. Let's commission an
            inventory of Oregon's assets on aging-in-place...let's show what we've got and what we
            are missing in terms of building out an R&amp;amp;D and new business incubation
            infrastructure for independent living technologies and services.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3. We need to identify, with our nursing and
            medical schools, what new kinds of careworkers and curriculums are needed to enable
            aging-in-place care for seniors (and people of all ages). If Oregon can develop the
            models for training and credentialing community workers and volunteers who can use these
            new technologies to do care delivery in the home, community, and electronically, then we
            will be the likely creator of the first national call center for electronic care
            &amp;amp; support for elders. With that asset, we would be a fierce competitor
            nationwide!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4. Let's make sure that our
            current and future technology infrastructure investments--for broadband, for Electronic
            Health Records, for insurance exchanges--are being designed and built to support
            aging-in-place and to carry data/transactions from hospital to home. If all we do is
            connect and coordinate care in hospitals and clinics, then we will fail to achieve the
            kind of health reform required to make us fiscally, morally, and medically
            strong.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5. We need to build upon
            ORCATECH to develop the nation's first 10,000 household cohort of seniors who can help
            test and prove the value of these aging-in-place technologies and care models. Today, we
            have about 300 households in the Portland metro area who are outfitted with these kinds
            of systems, but we need 10,000 homes across the state to deliver the statistical and
            economic data that proves which systems are most valuable, usable, and useful. If we
            build this kind of large-scale R&amp;amp;D infrastructure, it will be very difficult for
            any other state to supplant our position as a leader in this sector.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6. Like many other states are exploring, let's
            develop a policy framework for seniors in our state that makes aging-in-place a right.
            If we set that as an overarching policy goal, then it will help to guide our activities
            and priorities for the full range of services--meals, medication assistance,
            transportation, social support, mental health, healthcare, etc.--that are needed to give
            people a high quality of life at an affordable cost from a place of their
            choice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;7. Let's set an audacious
            goal--a 2020 vision--to move 50% of care in Oregon out of institutions and into homes
            and the community in 10 years. We may not achieve 50% or it may happen faster than 10
            years, but if we set a goal that everyone knows and can aim for, then we will achieve
            great progress towards an aging-in-place agenda!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;In closing, I want to reiterate a message I have played over and over again in
            the pages of these blog entries: we need to prepare for Global Aging much as we do
            Global Warming. Just as our state (and our nation), are competing to try to become a
            leader in Green Tech industries to address Global Warming, so too, we should be
            competing to become a leader in Gray Tech industries for Global Aging. The issues and
            needs are no less urgent or pervasive; the opportunities for economic growth for the
            state are no less promising. And if we are truly a state committed to healthcare reform,
            then let's make sure that commitment includes long term care as we figure out how to
            improve cost, quality, and access for people of all ages.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; Comments (1) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/b2gRGCsDtuY" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/2011/03/oregons_opportunity_for_innovating_aging_a_city_club_follow_up.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>

        <title type="html">Jewelry, Gold and Intel?</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/y5vdGCNDSVM/jewelry_gold_and_intel.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/csr//16.4628</id>

        <published>2011-03-28T16:21:22Z</published>
        <updated>2011-03-28T16:37:35Z</updated>

        <summary type="html">Intel has been working hard to set-up the systems and processes so we
            can source “conflict-free” tin, tantalum and tungsten - and we feel we have a pretty
            good plan for these metals. However, gold is particularly challenging because
            the...</summary>


        <author>

            <name>Gary Niekerk</name>


            <uri>http://blogs.intel.com/csr/2007/06/profile_garys_niekirk.php</uri>

        </author>



        <category term="general_csr" label="general_csr"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/general-csr//"/>

        <category term="conflcitminerals" label="conflcitminerals"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="conflictmetals" label="conflictmetals"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="conflictfree" label="conflictfree" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>


        <category term="gold" label="gold" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="responsiblesourcing" label="responsiblesourcing"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>

        <category term="supplychain" label="supplychain" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/csr/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;Intel has
            been working hard to set-up the systems and processes so we can source
            &amp;#8220;conflict-free&amp;#8221; tin, tantalum and tungsten - and we feel we have a
            pretty good plan for these metals. However, gold is particularly challenging because the
            vast majority of all gold goes into jewelry, not technology. Also, gold is so valuable
            that smuggling is a serious issue so tracking becomes a greater challenge. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;It quickly became clear to us that if we wanted to address the challenges
            related to responsible gold sourcing - we would need to bring together the biggest
            players in the gold and jewelry industry; so that&amp;#8217;s just what we did in a
            meeting last month in Denver. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On March 8th, 2011 companies from the
            electronics industry met with leading companies and associations from the gold and
            jewelry industries to share their knowledge and experience regarding responsible supply
            chain practices. Electronics companies shared their learning and latest initiatives to
            acquire responsibly-sourced minerals throughout their supply chains, particularly for
            tin and tantalum. Gold mining, jewelry and refining companies shared the knowledge and
            expertise gained in their efforts to validate responsibly-sourced supply chains for
            gold. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Attendees at the meeting included multi-national gold mining
            and refining companies, large and small jewelry retail and manufacturing chains, and
            representatives from leading industry organizations. The meeting was convened by Intel
            Corporation and hosted by Newmont Mining in its Denver offices. The collaboration
            between the various sectors was facilitated by RESOLVE, an organization that works to
            support critical policy initiatives, and advance collaborative learning and best
            practices. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The attendees at the meeting agreed to continue dialogue
            as they explore solutions. They discussed and evaluated processes to validate sources of
            responsibly mined gold and differentiate it from illicit sources. They will take
            appropriate next steps such as testing programs to validate sources and recognize
            responsible actors in the gold supply chain. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Participants will be
            reaching out to and welcome input from other related industries and stakeholders as part
            of this effort. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Participants included: Intel, HP, Birks, Johnson
            Matthey, AngloGold Ashanti, Kinross, Metalor, Newmont, Richline, Rio Tinto/Kennecott,
            Tiffany &amp;amp; Co., Responsible Jewellery Council, Valcambi, World Gold Council,
            RESOLVE and others.&lt;/p&gt; Comments (0) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/y5vdGCNDSVM" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://blogs.intel.com/csr/2011/03/jewelry_gold_and_intel.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>


    <entry>
        <title type="html">Future Lab: Intel Science Talent Search 2011</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/M5H3skurr6I/future_lab_intel_science_talen.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/research//17.4627</id>

        <published>2011-03-28T15:41:14Z</published>
        <updated>2011-03-28T15:52:14Z</updated>

        <summary type="html">Where do the inventors and researchers of the future come from? They
            are in high school right now! This year’s Intel Science Talent Search brought together
            kids from across the country who are doing research that will knock your
            socks...</summary>

        <author>

            <name>Cheryl Miller</name>


        </author>



        <category term="futurelab" label="futurelab" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/research/tag/"/>

        <category term="intelsciencetalentsearch" label="intelsciencetalentsearch"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/research/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;Where do the
            inventors and researchers of the future come from? They are in high school right now!
            This year&amp;#8217;s Intel Science Talent Search brought together kids from across the
            country who are doing research that will knock your socks off! We spoke with 3 finalists
            who are investigating such topics as formation of protein shapes in the human body,
            long-term impact of environmental cleanup using Organoclay, and alternative methods for
            approximating the square root of integers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is inspiring to see the
            enthusiasm and amazing work that these kids are bringing to their various fields of
            study. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Comments (0) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/M5H3skurr6I" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Researchintel/~3/hPNOhdhgSVs/future_lab_intel_science_talen.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Join us this Friday at the City Club of Portland - with Eric
            Dishman</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/TRtGYnKIIWM/join_us_this_friday_at_the_city_club_of_portland_-_dishman_speaking.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/healthcare//38.4621</id>

        <published>2011-03-21T15:42:28Z</published>
        <updated>2011-03-30T16:51:17Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"
            ><![CDATA[ Our planet is aging. 1 out of 7 people will be 65+ by 2025 and there will be a shortage of doctors, nurses, and midwives worldwide (*WHO reported that this shortage was already&nbsp; 4 million in 2006) to care...]]></summary>

        <author>

            <name>Charing Riolo</name>


        </author>




        <category term="healthcare" label="healthcare" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare//"/>

        <category term="dishman" label="dishman" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="health" label="health" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="healthpolicy" label="healthpolicy"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="healthcare" label="healthcare"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="orcatech" label="orcatech" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>

        <category term="portlandcityclub" label="portlandcityclub"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt;Our planet
            is aging. 1 out of 7 people will be 65+ by 2025 and there will be a shortage of doctors,
            nurses, and midwives worldwide (*WHO reported that this shortage was already&amp;nbsp; 4
            million in 2006) to care for them. With more and more care moving home, 1 out of 3
            American adults, 53 million people today deliver informal care. The value of the
            services family caregivers in the US provide for "free" is estimated to be $306 billion
            a year. Several factors like this are already pushing for the need to better manage our
            aging population and move traditional care to home-based models.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To learn more about this important topic,
            you&amp;nbsp;are invited to the City Club of Portland's Friday Forum on March
            25th.&amp;nbsp; To reserve your ticket &lt;a
            href="http://www.pdxcityclub.org/content/future-aging-through-technological-innovation"&gt;click
            here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Eric Dishman, Intel
            Fellow and Director of Health Innovation and Policy,&amp;nbsp;Intel Architecture Group,
            will discuss new "gray technologies" that may enhance social engagement, disease
            management, cognitive support and healthcare at home.&amp;nbsp; For the past 12 years,
            Intel researchers in Oregon--in collaboration with the Oregon Center for Aging and
            Technology (ORCATECH)--have studied the needs of more than 1000 elderly households in 20
            countries to invent and test out new technologies.&amp;nbsp; Dishman&amp;nbsp;will
            provide examples of research conducted and&amp;nbsp;he will also address how Oregon is
            at the forefront of developing new technologies, services, care models and jobs that
            address the challenge of global aging.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;If you are interested in attending this event, please&amp;nbsp; &lt;a
            href="http://www.pdxcityclub.org/content/future-aging-through-technological-innovation"&gt;click
            here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;*United nations department of economic and
            social affairs. 2007b&lt;/p&gt; Comments (1) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/TRtGYnKIIWM" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>

        <feedburner:origLink>http://blogs.intel.com/healthcare/2011/03/join_us_this_friday_at_the_city_club_of_portland_-_dishman_speaking.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title type="html">Smart Broadcasters are Adapting to Smart TV</title>
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html"
            href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~3/S46wGI1U6LA/smart_broadcasters_are_adaptin.php"/>
        <id>tag:blogs.intel.com,2011:/technology//10.4616</id>

        <published>2011-03-17T01:01:01Z</published>

        <updated>2011-03-16T12:13:15Z</updated>

        <summary type="html"> The television was the first screen to appear in our home, yet it has
            become the last to connect to the Internet. The first “connected” TV and Blu-ray players
            appeared in 2008 and, from the outset, they merely offered...</summary>

        <author>

            <name>Paul Tapp</name>


            <uri>http://www.facebook.com/IntelSmartTV</uri>

        </author>




        <category term="digital_home" label="digital_home"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/digital-home//"/>

        <category term="technologies_for_our_lives" label="technologies_for_our_lives"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/add-category//"/>

        <category term="broadband" label="broadband" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>

        <category term="broadcasters" label="broadcasters"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>

        <category term="connectedtv" label="connectedtv"
            scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>

        <category term="content" label="content" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>

        <category term="hollywood" label="hollywood" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>

        <category term="netflix" label="netflix" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>

        <category term="smarttv" label="smarttv" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>


        <category term="william" label="william" scheme="http://blogs.intel.com/technology/tag/"/>


        <content type="html" xml:lang="en" xml:base="http://blogs.intel.com/"> &lt;p&gt; The
            television was the first screen to appear in our home, yet it has become the last to
            connect to the Internet. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The first &amp;#8220;connected&amp;#8221;
            TV and Blu-ray players appeared in 2008 and, from the outset, they merely offered basic
            and limited content portals. They &lt;em&gt;couldn&amp;#8217;t&lt;/em&gt; do more
            because the processors inside a TV were designed to process &lt;em&gt;images&lt;/em&gt;;
            they were never intended to run the software or apps we use on the Internet. So the
            &amp;#8220;connected TV&amp;#8221; was - and still is - slow, complicated and limited in
            its capacity to drive change.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a
            href="http://scoop.intel.com/smart-tv-most-significant-change-tv-history/"&gt;Smart
            TV&lt;/a&gt; disrupts things, however, sporting fully capable browsers which flawlessly
            present the Internet videos and applications that we use daily. It enables genuinely new
            interactive and Internet-centric television experiences.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Immediate
            benefits of having fully Internet-capable TVs go far beyond being able to browse the
            web. Of course there are apps, games and huge social networking implications - and
            I&amp;#8217;ll cover these in future blogs. Hugely significant though, is that media
            conglomerates no longer determine which content will and will not be available on our TV
            sets. No longer confined to schedules, we can watch on demand. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Smart
            TV introduces a virtuous circle, which gives &lt;em&gt;consumers&lt;/em&gt; a lot more
            freedom and choice, whilst also enabling &lt;em&gt;content creators&lt;/em&gt; to reach
            new, global audiences.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Would be script-writers, playwrights, experts,
            comedians and a lot of other talent is entering the fray and producing innovative
            content for emerging audiences. We saw the dawn of this activity a couple of years ago
            with Joss Whedon&amp;#8217;s &lt;a
            href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dr._Horrible's_Sing-Along_Blog"&gt;Dr
            Horrible&lt;/a&gt; which according to a &lt;a
            href="http://blogs.forbes.com/michaelhumphrey/2010/11/08/who-can-save-google-tv-dr-horrible-thats-who"&gt;great
            blog&lt;/a&gt; on Forbes.com &amp;#8220;[took] six days, no budget and a lot of talent.
            Out came millions of viewers, brisk sales, and an Emmy&amp;#8221;. There are others too,
            like &lt;a href="http://www.watchtheguild.com/"&gt;The Guild&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a
            href="http://www.lstudio.com/web-therapy/introducing-web-therapy.html"&gt;Web
            Therapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now that we are free to watch such content on our
            TV sets, the creative floodgates have been opened. Check out the &lt;a
            href="http://www.laughfactory.com/"&gt;Laugh Factory&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a
            href="http://www.ifc.com/onn/"&gt;Onion News Network&lt;/a&gt; for example (preferably
            from your smart TV!) These content creators are now able to directly reach huge
            audiences, niche or otherwise, on a global scale without having to worry about whether
            they&amp;#8217;ll be able to sell their content to a TV network in order for it to get
            viewed. See what Black Eyed Peas frontman has to say about it in this &lt;a
            href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2woxmf38ekc&amp;amp;feature=player_detailpage#t=460s"&gt;interview
            with will.i.am&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Smart TV also enables an entire new line of
            independent broadcasters. &lt;a href="http://revision3.com/"&gt;Revision 3&lt;/a&gt;
            calls itself &amp;#8220;the leading television network for the internet
            generation&amp;#8221;. &lt;a href="http://smibs.tv/"&gt;smibs.tv&lt;/a&gt; has just
            materialised &amp;#8220;for people with a passion&amp;#8221;&amp;#8230; there are many
            others. Finally the .tv domain can live up to its destiny (sorry, Tuvaluans!) &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Content publishing is no longer in the hands of a select few. As more and more
            viewers have the means to easily watch Internet programming on the TV, more innovative
            broadcasts will emerge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And the more content that exists, the easier
            it will be for smart TVs to bring you content tailored to your preferences&amp;#8230; so
            they&amp;#8217;ll keep getting smarter.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Smart TV is redefining
            television as we know it. To keep up-to-date on the latest smart TV news and trends,
            follow the Intel smart TV team on &lt;a
            href="http://www.twitter.com/IntelSmartTV"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a
            href="http://www.facebook.com/IntelSmartTV"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;. If you want to learn
            more, check out this smart TV video.&lt;/p&gt; Comments (0) &lt;img
            src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/IntelBlogs/~4/S46wGI1U6LA" height="1"
            width="1"/&gt;</content>
        <feedburner:origLink>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TechnologyIntel/~3/Zx4aieXIHLw/smart_broadcasters_are_adaptin.php</feedburner:origLink>
    </entry>





</feed>
